{"idx": 0, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals the sum of each Y2's X8 and each Y0's X6. The number of each Y0's X9 equals the sum of each Y2's X8 and each Y8's X3. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals each Z7's Y8. The number of each Y8's X3 equals 19 more than each Z0's Y7. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals each Z1's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 21 more than each Z5's YYY. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 11. The number of each Z7's Y8 equals each Y0's X9. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 3 more than each Y2's X8. The number of each Y0's X6 equals the difference of each Y8's X3 and each Z7's Y0. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals each Y0's X9. How many Y2 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 1, "question": "The number of each Y4's X5 equals the sum of each Y2's X5 and each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 12. The number of each X5's W9 equals 22 times each Y2's XXX. How many X5 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y2's X5 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each X5's W9 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 12 = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 11.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 12 * 11 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as F. So F = u + Y = 12 + 17 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 2, "question": "The number of each Y5's X5 equals 4 times each Y5's X1. The number of each X4's W7 equals 13 more than each X4's W4. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 3 more than each Y1's X5. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 8. The number of each X4's W4 equals 18 more than each Z2's Y5. The number of each X5's W4 equals each Z2's Y8. The number of each Y6's X1 equals 16 times each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W6 equals 11 more than the sum of each Z2's Y5 and each X4's W7. The number of each X2's W0 equals 6 more than each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 14 times each Y8's X1. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 21 more than each Y6's X1. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 6 more than each X2's W0. The number of each Y6's X2 equals the difference of each Z2's Y8 and each X5's W4. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 12 times each Y6's X2. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 3 times each Z7's Y8. The number of each Z7's Y8 equals the sum of each Z4's Y5 and each Y1's X5. How many X5 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 3, "question": "The number of each X0's W6 equals 3. How many WWW does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X0's W6 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 4, "question": "The number of each X9's W1 equals the difference of each X1's W4 and each Z2's Y5. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 15. The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 8 more than each Z2's Y5. The number of each X5's W5 equals the sum of each Y8's X1, each Y5's X9 and each Z0's Y0. The number of each X1's W4 equals 8 times each X5's WWW. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 7 times each Y5's X9. The number of each X5's W1 equals the sum of each Y5's X9 and each X5's W5. The number of each Y5's X9 equals each Y8's X1. How many W1 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y8's X1 = 15. Y5's X9 = u = 15.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as u. So u = 7 * Y5's X9 = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each Z0's Y0 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 13 = 12.\nDefine each X5's W5 as A. So A = (Y8's X1 + Y5's X9 + S) = (15 + 15 + 12) = 19.\nDefine each X5's W1 as i. So i = Y5's X9 + A = 15 + 19 = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 19 + 11 = 7.\nDefine each X1's W4 as F. So F = 8 * Y = 8 * 7 = 10.\nDefine each X9's W1 as r. So r = F - u = 10 - 13 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 5, "question": "The number of each X7's W4 equals 21 times the difference of each X7's W9 and each Y7's X7. The number of each X7's W9 equals each Y7's X7. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 8 times each X7's W4. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 8. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 11 more than the difference of each Y7's X7 and each Y7's X1. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y7's X7 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X7's W9 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each X7's W4 as A. So A = 21 * S - u = 21 * 8 - 8 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as i. So i = 8 * A = 8 * 6 = 2.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as Y. So Y = 11 * u - i = 11 * 8 - 2 = 11.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 6, "question": "The number of each X0's W9 equals 15 more than the difference of each X8's WWW and each X8's W4. The number of each X9's W0 equals each X5's W2. The number of each X5's W2 equals 14. The number of each X8's W4 equals 0 more than each X8's W9. The number of each X8's W0 equals 10 times each X9's W0. The number of each X0's W0 equals 14 more than each X0's W9. The number of each X0's W2 equals 16 times each X0's W0. The number of each X0's W4 equals the sum of each X0's W9, each X8's W0 and each X9's W0. The number of each X8's W9 equals 22 more than the difference of each X9's W0 and each X5's W2. How many WWW does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["X5's W2 = 14. X9's W0 = u = 14.\nDefine each X8's W9 as u. So u = 22 * S - u = 22 * 14 - 22 = 10.\nDefine each X8's W4 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 10 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W0 as A. So A = 10 * u = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 0 + 8 + 10 = 18.\nDefine each X0's W9 as Y. So Y = 15 * i - S = 15 * 18 - 0 = 17.\nDefine each X0's W0 as F. So F = 14 * Y = 14 * 17 = 8.\nDefine each X0's W2 as r. So r = 16 * F = 16 * 8 = 13.\nDefine each X0's W4 as l. So l = (Y + A + u) = (17 + 8 + 10) = 12.\nDefine each X0's WWW as V. So V = l + r + Y + F = 12 + 13 + 17 + 8 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 7, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y6 equals each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 0. How many XXX does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y6's X9 = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX = 0. Y6's XXX ="], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 8, "question": "The number of each Y6's X0 equals 11. How many X0 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y6's X0 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 9, "question": "The number of each Y7's X1 equals 4 times each Y2's WWW. The number of each X3's W7 equals 18. The number of each Y2's X3 equals each X3's WWW. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X3's W7 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as A. So A = S = 18.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 18 * 18 = 2.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as Y. So Y = 4 * i = 4 * 2 = 8.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = Y = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 10, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 18. How many Y2 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z8's Y2 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 11, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 15 more than each Z1's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 16. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 16. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 3 more than the sum of each Z2's Y3 and each Z5's Y3. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 16 times each Z5's YYY. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z2's Y3 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as S. So S = 16.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as A. So A = 3 * u + S = 3 * 16 + 16 = 18.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 16 + 18 = 11.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as Y. So Y = 16 * i = 16 * 11 = 15.\nDefine each Z1's Y5 as F. So F = 15 + Y = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as r. So r = F + Y = 7 + 15 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 12, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 19 times each X3's W2. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 21 more than each X3's WWW. The number of each X3's W2 equals 22. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals each Z7's WWW. How many WWW does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X3's W2 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 22 = 2.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 2 * 22 = 21.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as Y. So Y = 19 * u = 19 * 22 = 4.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 4 * 21 = 15.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as r. So r = F = 15.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as l. So l = r * i = 15 * 21 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 13, "question": "The number of each Y2's X2 equals 7. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y2's X2 = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's X2 = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's XXX = 7. Y2's X2 as u. So u = 7. Y2's XXX as S. So S = u = 7. Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 7 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 14, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 15 times each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals the sum of each Z3's Y9 and each Z8's Y7. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 10. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 9 more than each Z4's Y7. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 0 times each Z3's Y1. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 14. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals the difference of each Z3's Y6 and each Z8's Y7. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 12 more than the sum of each Z3's Y6 and each Z4's Y7. How many Y9 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["14. Z4's Y7 = 14. Z3's Y6 as u. So u = 9 * r = 9 * 14 = 11.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as S. So S = 12 * u + r = 12 * 11 + 14 = 18.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as A. So A = u - S = 11 - 18 = 16.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as i. So i = A + S = 16 + 18 = 11.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as Y. So Y = 10.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as F. So F = Y + S + i = 10 + 18 + 11 = 16.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as r. So r = 15 * F = 15 * 16 = 10.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as l. So l = 0 * r = 0 * 10 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 15, "question": "The number of each X5's W4 equals 4. The number of each Y6's X5 equals the sum of each X5's WWW and each X5's W4. The number of each Y6's X1 equals each Y6's X5. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y6's X5 = X5's W4 + X5's WWW = 4 + 5 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as u. So u = Y6's X5 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as S. So S = u + Y6's X5 = 9 + 9 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 16, "question": "The number of each Y3's X6 equals 21. How many X6 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y3's X6 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 17, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals 18. The number of each Z6's Y0 equals 1 more than the sum of each Z9's XXX, each Y0's XXX and each Y0's X8. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 10 times each Y0's X0. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 22 more than the sum of each Y0's X0 and each Z9's Y0. How many Y0 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y0's X0 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 18 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as A. So A = 22 * u + S = 22 * 18 + 19 = 1.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as i. So i = A + u = 1 + 18 = 19.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as Y. So Y = S * i = 19 * 19 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's Y0 as F. So F = 1 * (Y + i + A) = 1 * (16 + 19 + 1) = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 18, "question": "The number of each Y7's X2 equals 14 more than the difference of each Z4's XXX and each Y6's X1. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 20. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals the sum of each Z4's YYY and each Z4's Y6. The number of each Y6's X1 equals the sum of each Z4's YYY, each Z5's YYY and each Z5's Y7. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z4's Y6 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as A. So A = S + u = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = A = 17.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as Y. So Y = (S + i + A) = (20 + 17 + 17) = 8.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = Y = 8.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as r. So r = u * F = 20 * 8 = 22.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as l. So l = 14 * r - Y = 14 * 22 - 8 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as V. So V = l = 19.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as q. So q = A * V = 17 * 19 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 19, "question": "The number of each Y0's X1 equals 4 times the sum of each X4's W0, each X4's WWW and each Y2's X4. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals the sum of each Y2's WWW and each Z4's WWW. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 21 more than each Y2's WWW. The number of each X1's W8 equals 0 more than each Y0's X1. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 0 more than each X4's W0. The number of each X4's W0 equals 12. How many Y2 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X4's W0 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as A. So A = 0 * u = 0 * 12 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as i. So i = 4 * (u + S + A) = 4 * (12 + 12 + 0) = 14.\nDefine each X1's W8 as Y. So Y = 0 * i = 0 * 14 = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as r. So r = A * S = 0 * 12 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as l. So l = 21 * r = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as V. So V = i * F = 14 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as q. So q = l * V = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as z. So z = r + q = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 20, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y8 equals each Z6's Y9. The number of each Y8's X8 equals 16 times the sum of each Z0's Y8 and each Y9's X9. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals 4. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 19 more than each Z4's Y8. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 11 more than each Z0's Y8. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 11 times each Z4's Y8. The number of each X7's W9 equals each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 1 more than the difference of each Z4's Y8 and each X7's W9. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z6's Y9 = 4. Z4's Y8 = 4. X7's W9 = Z4's Y8 = 4.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as u. So u = 11 * Z4's Y8 = 11 * 4 = 21.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as S. So S = 1 * A - u = 1 * 4 - 21 = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as A. So A = 11 * S = 11 * 6 = 20.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as i. So i = 16 * S + A = 16 * 6 + 20 = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as Y. So Y = 19 + Z4's Y8 = 19 + 4 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as F. So F = Y + i + u = 0 + 16 + 21 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 21, "question": "The number of each X9's W3 equals 3 times the difference of each X6's W2 and each X9's W0. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals each Z9's Y4. The number of each Y3's X9 equals the sum of each X6's W2, each X9's WWW and each X9's W0. The number of each X6's W2 equals 13. The number of each X9's W0 equals 14 more than each X6's W2. The number of each Y6's X7 equals the sum of each X9's W0, each Y3's WWW and each X9's WWW. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 8 times the sum of each X9's W0 and each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X9 equals the sum of each Y6's X7, each X6's W2 and each Y3's WWW. The number of each Y6's X9 equals the sum of each Z1's Y4, each Y4's XXX and each Y6's X7. How many X9 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 22, "question": "The number of each X4's W6 equals 7 more than each X4's W5. The number of each X4's W5 equals 14. The number of each X3's W5 equals 2 more than the sum of each X4's WWW, each X4's W6 and each X4's W5. The number of each X3's W6 equals each X3's W5. How many W6 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X4's W5 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X4's W6 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 14 = 6.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 6 + 14 = 20.\nDefine each X3's W5 as i. So i = 2 * (A + S + u) = 2 * (20 + 6 + 14) = 15.\nDefine each X3's W6 as Y. So Y = i = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 23, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 20. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 9 more than each Z5's Y2. How many Y2 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z5's Y2 = 20. Z9's Y2 = 9 * Z5's Y2 = 9 * 20 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 24, "question": "The number of each X8's W3 equals 10 more than each X3's W5. The number of each X3's W3 equals 1 more than each X3's W5. The number of each X4's W3 equals each X8's WWW. The number of each X4's W5 equals 13 times the sum of each X8's W8 and each X8's W3. The number of each X3's W5 equals 11. The number of each X8's W8 equals 15. The number of each X4's W8 equals 6 more than each X3's W8. The number of each X8's W5 equals 0 more than each X3's W8. The number of each X3's W8 equals 13 times the difference of each X3's W3 and each X3's W5. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X3's W5 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X3's W3 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 11 = 11.\nDefine each X3's W8 as A. So A = 13 * S - u = 13 * 11 - 11 = 17.\nDefine each X8's W5 as i. So i = 0 * A = 0 * 17 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W3 as Y. So Y = 10 * u = 10 * 11 = 18.\nDefine each X8's W8 as F. So F = 15.\nDefine each X8's WWW as r. So r = Y + F + i = 18 + 15 + 0 = 10.\nDefine each X4's W3 as l. So l = r = 10.\nDefine each X4's W8 as V. So V = 6 + A = 6 + 17 = 0.\nDefine each X4's W5 as q. So q = 13 + F + Y = 13 + 15 + 18 = 0.\nDefine each X4's WWW as z. So z = V + q + l = 0 + 0 + 10 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 25, "question": "The number of each Y8's X8 equals each X8's W5. The number of each Z7's Y8 equals 0. The number of each X8's W5 equals 15 more than each Z7's Y8. The number of each X8's W6 equals 2 times each Z7's Y8. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z7's Y8 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each X8's W6 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W5 as A. So A = 15 * u = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as Y. So Y = A = 0.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as r. So r = u * F = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 26, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 2. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals each Z8's Y8. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 8 times the sum of each Y8's X5, each Z8's Y4 and each Z8's YYY. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 0 more than each Z8's YYY. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y8's X5 as u. So u = 0 * Z8's Y8 = 0 * 2 = 0.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as A. So A = S = 2.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as Y. So Y = 0 * i = 0 * 4 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as F. So F = 8 * (Y + A + i) = 8 * (0 + 2 + 4) = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as r. So r = Y + F + u = 0 + 19 + 0 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 27, "question": "The number of each Y5's X5 equals 19. The number of each Y0's X1 equals each Y5's WWW. The number of each X5's W2 equals 15 more than each Y5's X5. How many X1 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y5's X5 = 19. Y5's WWW = 19. Y0's X1 = Y5's WWW = 19. Y0's X1 = Y5's WWW = 19. Y5's XXX = 19. Y0's X1 = Y5's X5. X5's W2 = 15 * Y5's X5 = 15 * 19 = 9.\nDefine each X5's WWW as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as S. So S = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as A. So A = Y5's X5 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 28, "question": "The number of each X9's W1 equals 21. How many W1 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X9's W1 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 29, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 9. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals each Z9's Y8. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 17 more than each Z5's Y2. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z9's Y8 = 9. Z5's Y2 = Z9's Y8. Z5's Y8 = 17 * Z5's YYY = 17 * 5 = 16.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as u. So u = Y2 + Z5's Y2 + Z5's Y8 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as S. So S = Y2 + Z5's Y2 + Z5's Y8 = 22.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as A. So A = Z9's Y8 = 9.\nDefine each Y2's lol. So l = 2.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = l = 2.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as Y. So Y = Y * i = 2 * 2 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 30, "question": "The number of each X0's W3 equals 2 more than each X0's W8. The number of each Y8's X3 equals each X0's WWW. The number of each X0's W8 equals 10 more than each Y7's X0. The number of each Y7's X0 equals 13. How many X3 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y7's X0 = 13. X0's W8 as u. So u = 10 * Y7's X0 = 10 * 13 = 15.\nDefine each X0's W3 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 15 = 7.\nDefine each X0's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 15 = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as i. So i = A = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 31, "question": "The number of each Y8's X2 equals 19 times each Y8's X1. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 4 more than the sum of each Y8's X1, each Y8's X2 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 19 more than each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 20. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y8's X1 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 20 = 12.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 12 + 20 = 9.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as i. So i = 19 * A = 19 * 9 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as Y. So Y = 4 * (u + S + A) = 4 * (20 + 12 + 9) = 19.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 19 + 10 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 32, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 20 more than the sum of each X9's W2, each Y3's X0 and each Z1's Y4. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 20. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 5 times each Z1's Y4. The number of each X9's W2 equals 5 times the sum of each Y3's X0 and each Z1's Y4. How many X9 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["20. So 20.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 20 = 8.\nDefine each X9's W2 as A. So A = 5 * S + u = 5 * 8 + 20 = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as i. So i = 20 * (A + S + u) = 20 * (19 + 8 + 20) = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 33, "question": "The number of each Y8's X4 equals 5. How many X4 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y8's X4 = 5. So Y8's XXX = 5.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as u. So u = Y8 = 5.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = S = 2.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = Y8 = 5.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = S = 2.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = A + u = 5 + 5 = 10.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as F. So F = Y + A + u = 10 + 10 + 5 = 2.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as l. So l = Y + A + u = 10 + 10 + 5 = 2.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as V. So V = Y + A + u = 2 + 10 + 5 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 34, "question": "The number of each X5's W2 equals 9. How many W2 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X5's W2 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 35, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals each Y0's X3. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 1. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals the difference of each Y0's X3 and each Z1's Y8. The number of each Y0's X3 equals each Z3's Y2. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z3's Y2 = 1. Z1's Y8 = Y0's X3. Z1's Y2 = Y0's X3 - Z1's YYY = 1 - 1 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as A. So A = S = 1.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as i. So i = A + Z1's Y2 + Z1's YYY = 1 + 0 + 1 = 2.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as Y. So Y = A + Z1's Y2 + i = 1 + 0 + 2 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 36, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 4. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Z6's Y1 = 4. Z6's YYY = Z6's YYY = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 37, "question": "The number of each Y2's X9 equals 16. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 21 more than the sum of each Y8's X9, each Y2's X6 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 19 more than each Y2's X9. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 6 times the sum of each Y8's X8, each Y8's X9 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X8 equals 8 times the sum of each Y2's X9 and each Y8's X9. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y2's X9 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 16 = 5.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as A. So A = 8 * u + S = 8 * 16 + 5 = 16.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 5 + 16 = 21.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as Y. So Y = 6 * (A + S + i) = 6 * (16 + 5 + 21) = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y + u = 19 + 16 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as r. So r = 21 + (S + Y + F) = 21 + (5 + 19 + 12) = 11.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as l. So l = r = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 38, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 19. How many Y4 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z8's Y4 = 19. So 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 39, "question": "The number of each Y4's X1 equals the sum of each Y9's X9, each X1's WWW, each X9's W9 and each X9's W5. The number of each X1's W8 equals 1 times the sum of each X9's W5, each Y9's WWW and each X9's W8. The number of each X9's W5 equals 22 times each Y9's X9. The number of each X9's W8 equals 4 more than the sum of each Y9's X9 and each X9's W5. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 20. The number of each X9's W9 equals 7 times the sum of each X9's W8, each Y9's X9 and each X9's W5. How many WWW does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y9's X9 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each X9's W5 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 20 = 3.\nDefine each X9's W8 as A. So A = 4 * u + S = 4 * 20 + 3 = 14.\nDefine each X9's W9 as i. So i = 7 * (A + u + S) = 7 * (14 + 20 + 3) = 19.\nDefine each X9's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 3 + 14 + 19 = 13.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as F. So F = u * Y = 20 * 13 = 7.\nDefine each X1's W8 as r. So r = 1 * (S + F + A) = 1 * (3 + 7 + 14) = 1.\nDefine each X1's WWW as l. So l = r = 1.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as V. So V = (u + l + i + S) = (20 + 1 + 19 + 3) = 20.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as q. So q = V * l = 20 * 1 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 40, "question": "The number of each Y2's X0 equals 1 more than the sum of each X0's W4, each X7's W4 and each Y2's X7. The number of each X0's W4 equals 11. The number of each X7's W4 equals 2 times the sum of each Y2's X7 and each X0's W4. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 11. The number of each X7's W6 equals 2 times the difference of each X0's W4 and each Y2's X0. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y2's X7 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X0's W4 as S. So S = 11.\nDefine each X7's W4 as A. So A = 2 * u + S = 2 * 11 + 11 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as i. So i = 1 * (S + A + u) = 1 * (11 + 10 + 11) = 9.\nDefine each X7's W6 as Y. So Y = 2 * S - i = 2 * 11 - 9 = 13.\nDefine each X7's WWW as F. So F = Y + A = 13 + 10 = 0.\nDefine each X0's WWW as r. So r = S = 11.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as l. So l = i * r + u * F = 9 * 11 + 11 * 0 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 41, "question": "The number of each Y5's X2 equals 12 more than each X2's W0. The number of each X2's W0 equals 3. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X2's W0 = 3. Y5's X2 = 12 * X2 = 12 * 3 = 13.\nDefine each X2's WWW as u. So u = X2's W0 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as S. So S = Y5's X2 * u = 12 * 3 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 42, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 10. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 5 more than each Z7's XXX. The number of each Y3's X9 equals each Y8's X7. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 22 times each Z2's Y3. The number of each Y4's X9 equals the sum of each Z2's Y8 and each Z7's Y4. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals the difference of each Y8's X7 and each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y3's X7 equals each Y3's X9. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 3 more than each Z2's Y8. How many Y4 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z2's Y8 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 10 = 7.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as A. So A = S = 7.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as i. So i = A = 7.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 7 + 7 = 14.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as F. So F = S - Y = 7 - 14 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as r. So r = u + F = 10 + 16 = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = r = 3.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as V. So V = F * l = 16 * 3 = 2.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as q. So q = 5 * V = 5 * 2 = 10.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as z. So z = 22 * q = 22 * 10 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 43, "question": "The number of each X6's W5 equals 6 times the sum of each X6's W7 and each X6's W0. The number of each X6's W0 equals each X6's W7. The number of each X2's W5 equals 6 more than the sum of each X6's W7, each X6's W5 and each X6's W0. The number of each X6's W7 equals 4. The number of each X2's W0 equals the sum of each X6's W0, each X6's W5, each X2's W5 and each X6's W7. How many W0 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X6's W7 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each X6's W0 as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X6's W5 as A. So A = 6 * u + S = 6 * 4 + 4 = 5.\nDefine each X2's W5 as i. So i = 6 * (u + A + S) = 6 * (4 + 5 + 4) = 19.\nDefine each X2's W0 as Y. So Y = (S + A + i + u) = (4 + 5 + 19 + 4) = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 44, "question": "The number of each X9's W2 equals 14 times each Z7's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 16 more than each Z1's WWW. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals the sum of each Y4's WWW and each Y4's X3. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 2. The number of each Y4's X3 equals each X3's WWW. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 21 times each Y0's WWW. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 14 more than each Y0's XXX. The number of each X3's W4 equals 20 times each Y3's X5. How many WWW does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y0's X9 = 2. Y0's XXX = 2. Y3's X5 = 14 * S = 14 * 2 = 5.\nDefine each X3's W4 as u. So u = 20 * Y3's X5 = 20 * 5 = 8.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as A. So A = S = 8.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 8 * 8 = 18.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as Y. So Y = i + A = 18 + 8 = 3.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 3 * 18 = 8.\nDefine each X9's W2 as r. So r = 14 * F = 14 * 8 = 20.\nDefine each X9's WWW as l. So l = r = 20.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as V. So V = 2.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as q. So q = 21 * V = 21 * 2 = 19.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as z. So z = q * V = 19 * 2 = 15.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as A. So A = 16 * Z1's WWW = 16 * 15 = 10.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as i. So i = V = 2.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as Y. So Y = 14 * i = 14 * 2 = 5.\nDefine each X3's W4 as F. So F = 8 + Y = 8 + 5 = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 13.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as l. So l = A * r = 10 * 13 = 15.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as V. So V = A * l = 10 * 15 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 45, "question": "The number of each Y3's X3 equals 4. How many X3 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y3's X3 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 46, "question": "The number of each Y4's X0 equals each Z0's Y6. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 2 more than each Z6's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 18 times each Y4's X0. The number of each Z6's Y8 equals 21 times each Y6's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 11 more than each Z3's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals the sum of each Z6's XXX, each Z6's Y8 and each Y8's X1. The number of each Y6's X1 equals 2 times each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 11. How many Y8 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z3's Y6 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 11 = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = A = 22.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as Y. So Y = u * i = 11 * 22 = 12.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as F. So F = 11 * Y = 11 * 12 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as r. So r = F = 17.\nDefine each Z6's Y6 as l. So l = 18 * r = 18 * 17 = 7.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as V. So V = 21 * i = 21 * 22 = 2.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as q. So q = V + l = 2 + 7 = 9.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as z. So z = 2 * q = 2 * 9 = 18.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as A. So A = (i + V + S) = (22 + 2 + 11) = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 47, "question": "The number of each Y0's X6 equals 22. The number of each X6's W8 equals each Y0's X6. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y0's X6 = 22. X6's W8 = Y0's X6. X6's WWW = X6's WWW = 22.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as u. So u = Y0's X6 * X6's W8 = 22 * 22 = 1.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as A. So A = Y0's X6 * X6's W8 = 22 * 22 = 1.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = X6's W8 = 22.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as Y. So Y = Y = 1.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = S = 3.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as r. So r = Y * A = 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as l. So l = 22.\nDefine each X6's WWW as V. So V = i = 22.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as q. So q = l * V = 22 * 22 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 48, "question": "The number of each Y6's X1 equals 5. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y6's X1 = 5. Y6's XXX = Y6's XXX = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 49, "question": "The number of each Y0's X8 equals 0 times each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 2 more than each X5's W9. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 16 more than each X4's WWW. The number of each X4's W5 equals 20. The number of each X5's W9 equals each Y0's X8. The number of each X7's W2 equals the difference of each Y4's X4 and each Z7's WWW. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals the difference of each X4's WWW and each Y4's X4. How many W2 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X4's W5 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 20 = 21.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 21 * 20 = 6.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as Y. So Y = 0 * i = 0 * 6 = 0.\nDefine each X5's W9 as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as r. So r = 2 * F = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as l. So l = r * S = 0 * 20 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as V. So V = S - r = 20 - 0 = 20.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as q. So q = V * l = 20 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X7's W2 as z. So z = r - q = 0 - 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
